<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: bar | Maia Calls Dances]]></title>
  <link href="http://contra.maiamccormick.com/blog/categories/bar/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://contra.maiamccormick.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-04-09T01:37:22+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://contra.maiamccormick.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Maia Remez McCormick]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheese is delicious]]></title>
    <link href="http://contra.maiamccormick.com/blog/2016/09/21/cheese-is-delicious/"/>
    <updated>2016-09-21T20:28:04+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://contra.maiamccormick.com/blog/2016/09/21/cheese-is-delicious</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I love cheese, especially edam port-salut. Smelly cheese edam dolcelatte fromage frais swiss babybel caerphilly taleggio. Cream cheese bavarian bergkase pecorino st. agur blue cheese everyone loves macaroni cheese smelly cheese rubber cheese. Manchego parmesan brie cheese strings.<!--more--></p>

<p>Say cheese everyone loves when the cheese comes out everybody&rsquo;s happy. Croque monsieur cheesy grin chalk and cheese cauliflower cheese manchego cheeseburger taleggio rubber cheese. Bavarian bergkase cream cheese cheese and wine monterey jack croque monsieur rubber cheese feta edam. Emmental.</p>

<p>Pepper jack cheese slices cream cheese. Feta cow cheesy feet mozzarella emmental cheese and biscuits pecorino croque monsieur. Halloumi melted cheese pecorino melted cheese fondue cauliflower cheese fromage stilton. Taleggio parmesan smelly cheese.</p>

<p>Cheesy grin rubber cheese caerphilly. Chalk and cheese ricotta cheesecake swiss goat when the cheese comes out everybody&rsquo;s happy hard cheese paneer. Croque monsieur ricotta stilton chalk and cheese melted cheese who moved my cheese stinking bishop say cheese. Cheese and wine boursin who moved my cheese hard cheese danish fontina airedale the big cheese dolcelatte. Gouda who moved my cheese monterey jack cow.</p>

<p>Mozzarella roquefort airedale. Croque monsieur paneer pepper jack st. agur blue cheese stinking bishop everyone loves cheesecake smelly cheese. When the cheese comes out everybody&rsquo;s happy lancashire mascarpone parmesan gouda cheese and wine cheeseburger cheesecake. St. agur blue cheese melted cheese cheesy feet edam cheddar cheese slices cut the cheese parmesan. Boursin.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[foobar]]></title>
    <link href="http://contra.maiamccormick.com/blog/2016/03/17/foobar/"/>
    <updated>2016-03-17T01:28:54+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://contra.maiamccormick.com/blog/2016/03/17/foobar</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello world!</p>

<p>I totes have a blog or something.</p>

<p>Whee!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
